free2peek.com 2012-10-03

# Privacy Statement

**PRIVACY STATEMENT**

In this statement International Media Company B.V. (which shall hereafter also be referred to as "IMC", "the company", "we", "us" or "our" as the case may be) sets out how we deal with the personal data of customers, visitors, users, and others who use www.free2peek.com (collectively or individually "Users"), we obtain via this website. 

The use of the website situated at the domain of [http://www.free2peek.com](http://www.free2peek.com/) and/or the software and any of the services and information thereof (collectively, the "F2P Website") provided by IMC are subject to the provisions of this Privacy Statement, including any amendments or updates hereto. This Privacy Statement is incorporated into and is subject to the Terms of Use of the F2P Website ( [Terms And Conditions](http://www.free2peek.com/tos.php) ). If you do not agree to this Privacy Statement, please do not use the F2P Website. 

Please note that any video, image, or other content posted at the direction of Users onto the F2P Website becomes published content and is not considered personally identifiable information subject to this Privacy Statement. 

**General  
** IMC takes your privacy seriously. We gather certain types of information about our Users and we want to help you understand the terms related to the collection and use of the information which we collect. This Privacy Statement discloses the types of information we gather, how we use it, and what choices you have regarding the collection of such information. BY USING, ACCESSING OR DOWNLOADING THE F2P WEBSITE, YOU AGREE TO THE COLLECTION AND USE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION (AS HEREUNDER DESCRIBED), ALL IN ACCORDANCE WITH THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS SET FORTH HEREUNDER. 

IMC reserves the right to modify the data protection measures and the present Privacy Statement at any time and w e shall notify you on any changes on the F2P Website and it is your responsibility to review this Privacy Statement for any changes. In general, we only use your personal information in the manner described in the Privacy Statement in effect when we received the personal information you provided. Your use of the F2P Website following any amendment of this Privacy Statement will signify your assent to and acceptance of its revised terms. 

**Collected information  
** When you submit personally identifiable information to us through the use of certain features on the F2P Website or by registering on this F2P Website, viewing or uploading video or photo content, posting messages in our forums or participating in a discussion, responding to surveys, making inquires on this F2P Website or subscribing to newsletters or other mailing lists, you may be asked to provide your first and last name, (email) address, username and a password. We use this information for the following purposes:  
to fulfill your requests for viewing video or photo content, programs, and the rendering of our digital teleservices;  
to communicate with you and respond to your inquiries;   
to conduct research about your use of the F2P Website;   
to operate, maintain and improve the features and functionality and content presented through the F2P Website;  
to help offer you other products, programs, or services that may be of interest;  
providing of data to third parties if required to do so by law or respond to a court order;  
providing information on content and services offered by us and other companies, selected by you on the basis of your personal preferences; in case you do not wish to receive this information, you can contact the customer service at customer@F2P.com 

Apart from this, we may ask you to provide information on your profession, position, age and personal interests. We use these data to gain a better insight into our Users and in order to further develop our services and improve our F2P Website and adapt it to your personal preferences. 

We collect and pass on only information that is necessary for exercising rights and meeting obligations resulting from the Terms of Use of the F2P Website ( [Terms And Conditions](http://www.free2peek.com/tos.php) ) and user agreement, and for reaching our legitimate business goals. 

Any personal information or video or photo content that you voluntarily disclose online (on discussion boards, in messages and forum areas, within your public profile page, etc.) becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others. Your account name (not your email address) is displayed to other Users when you upload video or photo material or send messages through the F2P Website and other Users can contact you through (unrequested) messages and comments. Any video or photo material that you submit to the F2P Website may be redistributed through the internet. IMC does not accept any responsibility or warranty for personal information disclosed to other users of F2P Website's discussion boards, chat-rooms or forums. 

We do not use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. We may, however, use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of major changes of the F2P Website or for customer service purposes). 

Please note that IMC may use your personally identifiable information to present offers to you on behalf of business partners and advertisers. However, while IMC's business partners and advertisers may receive aggregate data about F2P Website's Users, any personally identifiable information of yours will not be shared with third parties unless you have consented to the sharing of this information. 

Finally, we record information (including the IP-address used) for the purpose of collecting and analysing user statistics and for the protection of our F2P Website. 

**Cookies  
** On the F2P Website, we may use cookies that are saved by your browser on your computer. Cookies save information (such as the configurations of your pc and preferences indicated by you) so as to facilitate the next visit to our F2P Website. These data do not contain any information on your name, address or other personal information that you may have provided. You can configure your browser in such a way that you do not receive cookies during your visit to the F2P Website. If cookies are disabled, however, you may not be able to use all the features of the F2P Website, or may be denied access to parts of the F2P Website. 

**Third party ad servers  
** IMC allows other companies, known as third-party ad servers or ad networks, to help present advertisements online in connection with the F2P Website. These third-party ad servers or ad networks may use cookies or similar technologies to serve such advertisements, and to help measure and research the advertisements' effectiveness. The use of these technologies by these third party-ad servers or ad networks is subject to their own privacy policies, not IMC's. This Privacy Statement does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or websites. 

The F2P Website may contain links transferring you from this website to other websites. These websites linked to F2P Website are not within IMC's control, and it is possible that another privacy policy is applicable to these websites. This privacy policy is therefore applicable to personal data exclusively that are used and stored on the F2P Website or have been stored by IMC. Therefore IMC recommends you to take care when you visit another website or when you supply personal information. IMC excludes any responsibility or warranty for such other websites. 

**Transfer of the company  
** In case of the further growth and development of IMC, it is possible that one or more divisions or assets of the company are transferred to a third party. In such a case, the data of our Users will also be transferred, in which case the information could become subject to a different privacy policy. In the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors' rights generally, we may not be able to control how your personal information is treated, transferred, or used. 

**Transfer to countries outside the EU  
** For technical and operational reasons, it may be necessary to transfer your data to (servers of) affiliated companies in the United States or other countries outside Europe, in which the regulations on privacy protection may not offer the same measure of protection as the existing regulations in the European Union. We will, however, always take appropriate measures in order to guarantee proper protection of your personal data. The User explicitly exempts IMC from any liability or warranty resulting from different country-specific data protection requirements and regulations. 

**Security  
** IMC has implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect and safeguard the personally identifiable information under our control from unauthorized access, improper use or disclosure, unauthorized modification, unlawful destruction or accidental loss. All our personnel that have access to and are associated with the processing of your personally identifiable information are obligated to respect the confidentiality of the information. 

**Accessing and updating your data  
** In case you want to know which data we have recorded of which you are the subject, or if you want to change your data, please contact our customer service at customer@F2P.com. IMC will meet your request in a reasonable period of time and after proof of your identity provided that IMC does not infringe any legal provisions by doing so. Please note that deletion of your 

personally identifiable information from IMC's database will not prevent IMC from using gathered anonymous information. 

**Questions  
** In case you have any further questions on this Privacy Statement or on our privacy policy, please send an email to our customer service at customer@F2P.com. 

**Date last modified  
** The English version(s) of this Privacy Statement and the Terms of Use of the F2P Website [TOS](http://www.free2peek.com/tos.php) concerned will at all times prevail. This Privacy Statement was last modified March 16th, 2009.
